Guide to the Janet G. Travell papers, 1910-1997 MS0704.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Correspondence, 1920-1997; MS0704 Series 4; 16 Linear feet (Box 41, Box 40, Box 53, Box 54, Box 45, Box 44, Box 43, Box 42, Box 49, Box 48, Box 47, Box 46, Box 65, Box 52, Box 51, Box 50, Box 64, Box 63, Box 60, Box 59, Box 62, Box 61, Box 56, Box 55, Box 58, Box 57, Box 70, Box 71, Box 72, Box 66
  - Professional: Correspondence and brochures, 1983-1995 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Professional: Correspondence and papers - Simons, David, 1977-1990 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Professional: Correspondence and papers - Simons, David, 1977-1990 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Professional: Correspondence and papers - Simons, David, 1979-1990 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Correspondence and papers - Simons, David, 1979-1990 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Correspondence and papers -Simons, David, 1979-1995 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Correspondence and requests for reprints of articles, 1950-1960 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Correspondence and requests for reprints of articles, 1950-1960 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Correspondence and requests for reprints of articles, 1957-1960 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Correspondence and requests for reprints of articles, 1958-1960 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Correspondence and requests for reprints of articles, 1960 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Professional: Correspondence and requests for reprints on painless injection articles, 1949-1957 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Professional: Correspondence- Ashkenaz, David M. (Wyeth Laboratories ), 1950-1957 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Correspondence- Authors Guild, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Correspondence- Bulpitt, Stanley, 1946-1970 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Correspondence for House Beautiful article, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Correspondence- Margoles, Michael, 1987-1991 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Correspondence- Readers Digest, 1969-1973 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Correspondence regarding CBS program "Mystery of Pain", 08/1971 -10/1971 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Correspondence regarding Dr. Travell's autobiography, Office Hours: Day and Night, 1969-1975 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Professional: Correspondence regarding Dr. Travell's autobiography, Office Hours: Day and Night, 1965-1983 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Professional: Correspondence regarding Dr. Travell's distribution of her autobiography, 1970-1972 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Professional: Correspondence- Robitscher, Jonas, 1974-1976 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Professional: Correspondence seeking permission for excerpt publication rights in Management of Skeletal Pain, 1958-1960 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Professional: Correspondence- Smith, Kline, and French Laboratories, 1955-1960 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Professional: Correspondence with "case report" patients, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Professional: Correspondence with David Simons et al regarding Trigger Point Manual, 1975-1990 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Correspondence with David Simons et al regarding Trigger Point Manual, 1974-1979 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Correspondence with dentists, 1976-1980 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Correspondence with John Mennell, V.A. Hospital, Martinez, CA, 1973-1974 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Correspondence, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Correspondence, articles, and booklets, 1943-1988 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Correspondence, articles, and booklets, 1943-1988 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Garb, Dr. Solomon - correspondence, 1949-1960 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Professional: George Washington University - correspondence, articles, etc., 1961-1981 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Professional: George Washington University - correspondence, articles, etc., 1961-1981 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Professional: Karp, Dorothy - Correspondence and Article, 1953 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1978-1992 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    Including 1981 article on Bonnie Prudden
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence and articles, 1945-1980 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence and Certificates/Licenses, 1964-1994 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence and Christmas cards, 1950-1994 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence and Christmas cards, 1960-1972 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence and clippings, 1945-1965 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence and clippings, 1961-1974 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence and papers, 1950-1993 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence and papers, 1950-1993 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence and Reports, 1980-1994 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence and Reports, 1980-1994 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence and reports, 1986-1992 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence and Travell's requests for reprints, 1977-1986 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence including an address by Robert Kennedy to University of Georgia Law School (05/06/1961), 1951-1964 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, X-Y-Z, 1966-1971 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1933-1940 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1941 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1942 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1945-1949 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1950 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1954 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1957 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1959 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    [For 1961-65, see also Series V Correspondence]
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1966 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1966 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Obituaries and funeral service programs for Janet Travell, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Professional: Miscellaneous personal correspondence, including copy of Wellesley transcript and c.v., 1970-1995 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Professional: Patient correspondence, 1957-1987 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Professional: Professional correspondence and clippings, 1961-1969 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Professional: Professional Memberships - correspondence and cards, 1949-1965 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Professional: Requests for reprints (incoming and outgoing), 1953-1955 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Professional: Requests for reprints by Dr. Travell, 1970-1993 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Professional: Requests for reprints of article written by Janet Travell, 1955 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Professional: Rudd, Jacob L., 1965-1969 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Professional: Speaking invitations declined, 1981-1984 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Professional: Tobacco Industry Research Committee Grant - Correspondence and Notes, 1955-1959 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Professional: Zohn, David A., 1969-1995 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Personal: Correspondence - Bates, Charles C. (step-nephew of Dr. Travell), 1974 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Personal: Correspondence - Bates, Talcott, 1949-1960 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Personal: Correspondence and obituary - Bates, Talcott (step-brother of Dr. Travell), 1960-1985 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Personal: Correspondence - Davidson, George (Dr. Travell's uncle), 1944 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Personal: Correspondence - Family, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Personal: Correspondence - Family, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Personal: Correspondence - Family, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Personal: Correspondence - McAlee, Richie (Dr. Travell's grandson), 1967-1973 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Personal: Correspondence - Pinci, Janet (Dr. Travell's daughter), 1971 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Personal: Correspondence - Pinci, Janet Powell McAlee, 1961-1969 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Personal: Correspondence - Weeks, Virginia D., 1955-1958 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Personal: Correspondence of Janet Travell, 1920-1921 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Personal: Correspondence of Janet Travell, 1921-1922 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Personal: Correspondence with family (Janet Pinci), 1965-1968 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Personal: Correspondence with family (Janet Pinci), 1969-1986 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Personal: Correspondence with family (Virginia Powell Street), 1950-1987 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Personal: Correspondence with family and appointment book, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Personal: Correspondence with family, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Personal: Correspondence with family, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Personal: Correspondence with family, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Personal: Correspondence with family, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Personal: Correspondence with family, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Personal: Correspondence with family, 1970-1997 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Personal: Early Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Personal: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1926-1982 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- White House years, 1950-1997; MS0704 Series 5; 6.5 Linear feet (Box 84, Box 82, Box 83, Box 80, Box 81, Box 78, Box 79, Box 75, Box 74, Box 77, Box 76, Box 73, Box 72)
  This series consists of lectures, programs, correspondence, newspaper articles, magazine articles, notes, invitations, receipts, research documents, and trip itineraries. This material dates from 1950-97, although the files primarily cover the time period when Dr. Travell worked in the White House. Many of the letters received by Dr. Travell were from people all over the world giving and asking advice regarding various medical ailments. These include letters from India, Argentina, France, Italy, Germany, Greece, Korea, Hong Kong, Columbia, England, Austria, Belgium, and Chile. There is also correspondence regarding rocking chairs popularized by President Kennedy.
  - White House Years: Albert Einstein College of Medicine, Yeshiva University - luncheon, 04/19/1961 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - White House Years: American Society for Tropical Medicine meeting, 11/01/1961 -11/04/1961 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - White House Years: Anderson Orthopedic Clinic lecture on Myofascial Pain, Arlington, VA, 02/08/1962 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - White House Years: Arthritis Foundation Physical Medicine lecture notes, 10/1962 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - White House Years: Camp Beckett Physical Fitness Institute, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - White House Years: Columbia University Career Day, 04/22/1961 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - White House Years: Dr. Travell's Commencement address at Meharry College, Nashville, TN, 06/05/1961 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - White House Years: Fiftieth Anniversary Celebration of the Children's Bureau, 04/09/1962 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - White House Years: Fortieth Anniversary Committee Honoring Dr. Gordon S. Seagrave (work in Burma), 1962 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - White House Years: Group Health Association lecture, Washington, DC, 02/14/1963 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - White House Years: Medical International Cooperation Organization (MEDICO), 1961 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - White House Years: Myofascial Pain lecture, San Antonio, TX, 10/21/1961 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - White House Years: National Naval Medical Center lecture on TMJ Pain, Bethesda, MD, 05/17/1961 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - White House Years: Osteopathy Conference, New York, 02/16/1961 -02/18/1961 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - White House Years: Photos of lantern slides used in seat design lectures, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - White House Years: President's Commission on Employment of Physically Handicapped, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - White House Years: President's Commission on Heart Disease, Cancer and Stroke, 1961-1964 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - White House Years: President's Commission on Status of Women, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - White House Years: President's Commission on Traffic Safety, 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - White House Years: President's Council on Youth Fitness, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - White House Years: President's Science Advisory Commission, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - White House Years: Program for Federal Woman's Award Dinner, 05/02/1963 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - White House Years: School of Medicine, University of Maryland (Baltimore) lecture, 03/15/1963 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - White House Years: State University of Iowa Hospital lecture, 10/05/1962 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - White House Years: State University of Iowa Hospital lectures, 11/07/1963 -11/09/1963 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - White House Years: Takoma Clinic lecture, Takoma Park, MD, 02/23/1965 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - White House Years: Travis Air Force Base (CA) Hospital lecture, 11/08/1962 -11/09/1962 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - White House Years: Travis evening lecture "The Importance of Sitting Comfortably", 11/09/1962 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - White House Years: USAF School of Aerospace Medicine in San Antonio - seminar, 05/1963 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - White House Years: USAF Symposium on Muskuloskeletal Problems and disorders, Lackland AFB, San Antonio, TX, 06/18/1962 -06/19/1962 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - White House Years: Washington Wellesley Club lecture, 11/18/1964 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - White House Years: White House Conference on Narcotic and Drug Abuse, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - White House Years: Y.W.C.A. Lectures, Washington, DC, 1961-1965 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - Mc, 1961-1964 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - A, 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - B, 1953-1965 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - B, 1953-1965 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - C, 1961-1964 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - C, 1961-1964 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - D, 1961-1964 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - E, 1961-1963 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - F, 1961-1964 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - Food and Drug Administration, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - Friends, A-G, 1961-1963 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - Friends, A-G, 1961-1963 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - Friends, O-Z, 1961-1964 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - G, 1961-1962 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - H, 1961-1964 (Box 75, Folder 3)